<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Frosty the snowman</title>
      <link>/songs/frosty-the-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/frosty-the-snowman/</guid>
      <description>G Thumpety thump thump, thumpety thump thump, D7 Look at Frosty go. Thumpety thump thump, thumpety thump thump, G over the hills of snow...Oh...Oh...over the hills of snow. G C G Frosty the Snow Man, was a jolly happy soul C G With a corn-cob pipe and a button nose D G and two eyes made out of coal. G C G Frosty the Snow Man, is a fairy tale they say C G He was made of snow but the children know C D7 G how he came to life one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle bells</title>
      <link>/songs/jingle-bells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/jingle-bells/</guid>
      <description>G Dashing through the snow C In a one horse open sleigh D O&#39;er the fields we go G Laughing all the way G Bells on bob tails ring C Making spirits bright C D What fun it is to laugh and sing C G A sleighing song tonight G Oh, jingle bells, jingle bells G Jingle all the way C G Oh, what fun it is to ride D D In a one horse open sleigh G Jingle bells, jingle bells G Jingle all the way C G Oh, what fun it is to ride D C G In a one horse open sleigh (lesser-known verses follow with the same chord structure) A day or two ago I thought I&#39;d take a ride And soon, Miss Fanny Bright Was seated by my side, The horse was lean and lank Misfortune seemed his lot He got into a drifted bank And then we got upsot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow</title>
      <link>/songs/let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>G Oh, the weather outside is frightful, D But the fire is so delightful, Am E7 Am And since we&#39;ve no place to go, D7 Bm G Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow. G It doesn&#39;t show signs of stopping, D And I brought some corn for popping. Am E7 Am The lights are turned way down low, D7 Bm G Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow D When we finally kiss good night, Em A7 D How I&#39;ll hate going out in the storm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockin&#39; around the Christmas tree</title>
      <link>/songs/rockin-around-the-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/rockin-around-the-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>C G Rocking around the Christmas tree at the Christmas party hop G C Mistletoe hung where you can see every couple tries to stop C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, let the Christmas spirit ring G C Later we&#39;ll have some pumpkin pie and we&#39;ll do some caroling F Em You will get a sentimental feeling when you hear Am D G Voices singing let&#39;s be jolly, deck the halls with boughs of holly C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, have a happy holiday G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old-fashioned way F Em You will get a sentimental feeling when you hear Am D G Voices singing let&#39;s be jolly, deck the halls with boughs of holly C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, have a happy holiday G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old-fashioned way G C G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old - fa - shioned way  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer</title>
      <link>/songs/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/</guid>
      <description>F Em Dm C You know Dasher and Dancer and Prancer and Vixen F Em Dm C Comet and Cupid and Donner and Blitzen Am Dm But do you recall D7 G7 The most famous reindeer of all? C Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer G Had a very shiny nose G And if you ever saw it C You would even say it glows C All of the other reindeer G Used to laugh and call him names G They never let poor Rudolph C Join in any reindeer games F Em Then one foggy Christmas Eve Dm7 G C Santa came to say: G &amp;quot;Rudolph with your nose so bright D7 G7 Won&#39;t you guide my sleigh tonight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus is coming to town</title>
      <link>/songs/santa-claus-is-coming-to-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/santa-claus-is-coming-to-town/</guid>
      <description>Intro: |C Am |Dm |C |G | Verse 1: C F You better watch out, you&#39;d better not cry, C F you&#39;d better not pout, I&#39;m telling you why, C Am Dm G C Santa Claus is coming to town. (Gather &#39;round...) C F He&#39;s making a list and checking it twice, C F C Am Dm G C gonna find out who&#39;s naughty and nice, Santa Claus is coming to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter wonderland</title>
      <link>/songs/winter-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/winter-wonderland/</guid>
      <description> D Sleigh bells ring are you listening A In the lane snow is glistening A7 Em A A7 A beautiful sight we&#39;re happy tonight Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland D Gone away is the blue bird A In his place is the new bird A7 Em A A7 Hes singing our song as we go along Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland Chorus: F# B F# In the meadow we can build a snowman F# B F# Then pretend that he is Parson Brown A D A He&#39;ll say Are you married We&#39;ll say No man A7 E A But you can do the job when you&#39;re in town D Later on we&#39;ll conspire A As we dream by the fire A7 Em A A7 To face unafraid the plans that we made Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>