<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rock on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/tags/rock/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rock on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/rock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cortez the killer</title>
      <link>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</guid>
      <description>He came dancing across the water With his galleons and guns Looking for the new world In that palace in the sun On the shore lay Montezuma With his coca leaves and pearls In his halls he often wondered With the secrets of the worlds And his subjects Gathered around him Like the leaves around a tree In their clothes of many colors For the angry gods to see And the women all were beautiful And the men stood Straight and strong They offered life in sacrifice So that others could go on Hate was just a legend And war was never known The people worked together And they lifted many stones They carried them To the flat lands And they died along the way But they built up With their bare hands What we still can&#39;t do today And I know she&#39;s living there And she loves me to this day I still can&#39;t remember when Or how I lost my way He came dancing across the water Cortez, Cortez What a killer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down by the river</title>
      <link>/songs/down-by-the-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/down-by-the-river/</guid>
      <description>Be on my side, I&#39;ll be on your side, baby There is no reason for you to hide It&#39;s so hard for me staying here all alone When you could be taking me for a ride. Yeah, she could drag me over the rainbow, send me away Down by the river I shot my baby Down by the river, Dead, oh, shot her dead. You take my hand, I&#39;ll take your hand Together we may get away This much madness is too much sorrow It&#39;s impossible to make it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman behind the counter in a small town</title>
      <link>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</guid>
      <description>I seem to recognize your face Haunting, familiar yet I can&#39;t seem to place it Cannot find the candle of thought to light your name Lifetimes are catching up with me All these changes taking place I wish I&#39;d seen the place But no one&#39;s ever taken me Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away I swear, I recognize your breath Memories like fingerprints are slowly raising Me, you wouldn&#39;t recall for I&#39;m not my former It&#39;s hard when you&#39;re stuck upon the shelf I changed by not changing at all Small town predicts my fate Perhaps that&#39;s what no one wants to see I just want to scream hello My God it&#39;s been so long Never dreamed you&#39;d return But now here you are and here I am Hearts and thoughts they fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feelin&#39; alright</title>
      <link>/songs/feelin-alright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/feelin-alright/</guid>
      <description>Seems I got to have a change of scene &#39;Cause every night I have the strangest dreams Imprisoned by the way it could have been Left here on my own or so it seems I got to leave before I start to scream But someone&#39;s locked the door and took the key You feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Well, you feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Boy you sure took me for one big ride Even now I sit and wonder why And when I think of you I start myself to cry out I just can&#39;t waste my time, I must keep dry Gotta stop believin&#39; in all your lies &#39;Cause there&#39;s too much to do before I die, hey You feelin&#39; alright?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Joe</title>
      <link>/songs/hey-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/hey-joe/</guid>
      <description>Hey Joe, where you goin&#39; with that gun of yours? Hey Joe, I said where you goin&#39; with that gun in your hand, oh I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man And that ain&#39;t too cool Huh, hey Joe, I heard you shot your mamma down You shot her down now Hey Joe, I heard you shot your lady down You shot her down in the ground, yeah Yeah Yes, I did, I shot her You know I caught her messin&#39; round, messin&#39; round town Yes I did, I shot her You know I caught my old lady messin&#39; &#39;round town And I gave her the gun And I shot her Alright Shoot her one more time again, baby Yeah Oh, dig it Oh, alright Hey Joe Where you gonna run to now, where you gonna go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layla</title>
      <link>/songs/layla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/layla/</guid>
      <description>What&#39;ll you do when you get lonely And nobody&#39;s waiting by your side? You&#39;ve been running and hiding much too long. You know it&#39;s just your foolish pride. Layla, you&#39;ve got me on my knees. Layla, I&#39;m begging, darling please. Layla, darling won&#39;t you ease my worried mind. I tried to give you consolation When your old man had let you down. Like a fool, I fell in love with you, Turned my whole world upside down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little wing</title>
      <link>/songs/little-wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/little-wing/</guid>
      <description>Well she&#39;s walking through the clouds With a circus mind That&#39;s running wild Butterflies and zebras and moonbeams And fairly tales, That&#39;s all she ever thinks about Riding the wind When I&#39;m sad she comes to me With a thousand smiles She gives to me free It&#39;s alright, she says It&#39;s alright Take anything you want from me Anything Fly on, little wing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melissa</title>
      <link>/songs/melissa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/melissa/</guid>
      <description>Crossroads, seem to come and go, yeah The gypsy flies from coast to coast Knowing many, loving none Bearing sorrow, having fun But, back home he&#39;ll always run To sweet Melissa Freight train, each car looks the same, all the same And no one knows the gypsy&#39;s name And no one hears his lonely sighs There are no blankets where he lies Lord, in his deepest dreams the gypsy flies With sweet Melissa Again, the mornin&#39;s come Again, he&#39;s on the run A sunbeam&#39;s shinin&#39; through his hair Fear not to have a care Well, pick up your gear and gypsy roll on Roll on Crossroads, will you ever let him go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No expectations</title>
      <link>/songs/no-expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/no-expectations/</guid>
      <description>Take me to the station And put me on a train I&#39;ve got no expectations To pass through here again Once I was a rich man and Now I am so poor But never in my sweet short life Have I felt like this before You heart is like a diamond You throw your pearls at swine And as I watch you leaving me You pack my peace of mind Our love was like the water That splashes on a stone Our love is like our music It&#39;s here, and then it&#39;s gone So take me to the airport And put me on a plane I&#39;ve got no expectations To pass through here again  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple rain</title>
      <link>/songs/purple-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/purple-rain/</guid>
      <description>   I never meant to cause you any sorrow I never meant to cause you any pain I only wanted to one time to see you laughing I only wanted to see you Laughing in the purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain I only wanted to see you Bathing in the purple rain I never wanted to be your weekend lover I only wanted to be some kind of friend Baby, I could never steal you from another It&#39;s such a shame our friendship had to end Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain I only wanted to see you Underneath the purple rain Honey, I know, I know I know times are changing It&#39;s time we all reach out For something new, that means you too You say you want a leader But you can&#39;t seem to make up your mind I think you better close it And let me guide you to the purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain If you know what I&#39;m singing about up here C&#39;mon, raise your hand Purple rain, purple rain I only want to see you Only want to see you In the purple rain  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>River of deceit</title>
      <link>/songs/river-of-deceit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/river-of-deceit/</guid>
      <description>My pain is self-chosen At least, so the prophet says I could either burn Or cut off my pride and buy some time A head full of lies is the weight, tied to my waist The river of deceit pulls down, oh oh The only direction we flow is down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down My pain is self-chosen At least I believe it to be I could either drown Or pull off my skin and swim to shore Now I can grow a beautiful shell for all to see The river of deceit pulls down, yeah The only direction we flow is down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down The pain is self-chosen, yeah Our pain is self-chosen Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susie Q</title>
      <link>/songs/susie-q/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/susie-q/</guid>
      <description>Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q baby I love you, Susie Q I like the way you walk I like the way you talk I like the way you walk I like the way you talk, Susie Q Well, say that you&#39;ll be true Well, say that you&#39;ll be true Well, say that you&#39;ll be true and never leave me blue, Susie Q Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine, Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine, baby all the time, Susie Q Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q, baby I love you, Susie Q I like the way you walk I like the way you talk I like the way you walk I like the way you talk, Susie Q Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q, baby I love you, Susie Q  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The needle and the damage done</title>
      <link>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</guid>
      <description>Intro: D D/C D/B D/Bb C C7 Esus4 E D D/C I caught you knockin&#39; at my cellar door D/B D/Bb &amp;quot;I love you, baby. Can I have some more?&amp;quot; C F Esus4 E Ooh, ooh, the damage done I hit the city and I lost my band I watched the needle take another man Gone, gone, the damage done [Repeat Intro] I sing the song, because I love the man I know that some of you don&#39;t understand Milk-blood to keep from running out I&#39;ve seen the needle and the damage done A little part of it in everyone But every junkie&#39;s like a settin&#39; sun  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under the bridge</title>
      <link>/songs/under-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/under-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel Like I don&#39;t have a partner Sometimes I feel Like my only friend Is the city I live in The city of angels Lonely as I am Together we cry I drive on her streets &#39;Cause she&#39;s my companion I walk through her hills &#39;Cause she knows who I am She sees my good deeds And she kisses me windy I never worry Now that is a lie I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way (yeah yeah) It&#39;s hard to believe That there&#39;s nobody out there It&#39;s hard to believe That I&#39;m all alone At least I have her love The city she loves me Lonely as I am Together we cry I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way (yeah yeah) Ooh no (no no yeah yeah) Love me I say yeah yeah Under the bridge downtown Is were I drew some blood Under the bridge downtown I could not get enough Under the bridge downtown Forgot about my love Under the bridge downtown I gave my life away (yeah yeah) Ooh no (no no yeah yeah) Here I stay yeah yeah Here I stay  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whipping post</title>
      <link>/songs/whipping-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/whipping-post/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been run down and I&#39;ve been lied to. And I don&#39;t know why, I let that mean woman make me a fool. She took all my money, wrecks my new car. Now she&#39;s with one of my good time buddies, They&#39;re drinkin in some cross-town bar. Sometimes I feel, sometimes I feel, Like I been tied to the whippin&#39; post. Tied to the whippin&#39; post, tied to the whippin&#39; post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild horses</title>
      <link>/songs/wild-horses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/wild-horses/</guid>
      <description>Childhood living is easy to do The things you wanted I bought them for you Graceless lady you know who I am You know I can&#39;t let you slide through my hands Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away I watched you suffer a dull aching pain Now you&#39;ve decided to show me the same No sweeping exit or offstage lines Could make me feel bitter or treat you unkind Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away I know I&#39;ve dreamed you a sin and a lie I have my freedom but I don&#39;t have much time Faith has been broken tears must be cried Let&#39;s do some living after we die Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses we&#39;ll ride them some day Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses we&#39;ll ride them some day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wish you were here</title>
      <link>/songs/wish-you-were-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/wish-you-were-here/</guid>
      <description>So, so you think you can tell Heaven from hell Blue skies from pain Can you tell a green field From a cold steel rail? A smile from a veil? Do you think you can tell? Did they get you to trade Your heroes for ghosts? Hot ashes for trees? Hot air for a cool breeze? Cold comfort for change? Did you exchange A walk on part in the war For a lead role in a cage?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>