<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fast on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/tags/fast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fast on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/fast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Feelin&#39; alright</title>
      <link>/songs/feelin-alright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/feelin-alright/</guid>
      <description>Seems I got to have a change of scene &#39;Cause every night I have the strangest dreams Imprisoned by the way it could have been Left here on my own or so it seems I got to leave before I start to scream But someone&#39;s locked the door and took the key You feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Well, you feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Boy you sure took me for one big ride Even now I sit and wonder why And when I think of you I start myself to cry out I just can&#39;t waste my time, I must keep dry Gotta stop believin&#39; in all your lies &#39;Cause there&#39;s too much to do before I die, hey You feelin&#39; alright?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use me</title>
      <link>/songs/use-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/use-me/</guid>
      <description>My friends feel it&#39;s their appointed duty They keep trying to tell me all you want to do is use me But my answer yeah to all that use me stuff Is I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up My brother sit me right down and he talked to me He told me that I ought not to let you just walk on me And I&#39;m sure he meant well yeah but when our talk was through I said brother if you only knew you&#39;d wish that you were in my shoes You just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Oh sometimes yeah it&#39;s true you really do abuse me You get in a crowd of high class people and then you act real rude to me But oh baby baby baby baby when you love me I can&#39;t get enough I and I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Talking about you using me but it all depends on what you do It ain&#39;t too bad the way you&#39;re using me &#39;Cause I sure am using you to do the things you do Ah ha to do the things you do  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whipping post</title>
      <link>/songs/whipping-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/whipping-post/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been run down and I&#39;ve been lied to. And I don&#39;t know why, I let that mean woman make me a fool. She took all my money, wrecks my new car. Now she&#39;s with one of my good time buddies, They&#39;re drinkin in some cross-town bar. Sometimes I feel, sometimes I feel, Like I been tied to the whippin&#39; post. Tied to the whippin&#39; post, tied to the whippin&#39; post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>