<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jimi Hendrix on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/artist/jimi-hendrix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jimi Hendrix on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/artist/jimi-hendrix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Joe</title>
      <link>/songs/hey-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/hey-joe/</guid>
      <description>Hey Joe, where you goin&#39; with that gun of yours? Hey Joe, I said where you goin&#39; with that gun in your hand, oh I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man And that ain&#39;t too cool Huh, hey Joe, I heard you shot your mamma down You shot her down now Hey Joe, I heard you shot your lady down You shot her down in the ground, yeah Yeah Yes, I did, I shot her You know I caught her messin&#39; round, messin&#39; round town Yes I did, I shot her You know I caught my old lady messin&#39; &#39;round town And I gave her the gun And I shot her Alright Shoot her one more time again, baby Yeah Oh, dig it Oh, alright Hey Joe Where you gonna run to now, where you gonna go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little wing</title>
      <link>/songs/little-wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/little-wing/</guid>
      <description>Well she&#39;s walking through the clouds With a circus mind That&#39;s running wild Butterflies and zebras and moonbeams And fairly tales, That&#39;s all she ever thinks about Riding the wind When I&#39;m sad she comes to me With a thousand smiles She gives to me free It&#39;s alright, she says It&#39;s alright Take anything you want from me Anything Fly on, little wing  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>