<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neil Young on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/artist/neil-young/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Neil Young on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/artist/neil-young/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cortez the killer</title>
      <link>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</guid>
      <description>He came dancing across the water With his galleons and guns Looking for the new world In that palace in the sun On the shore lay Montezuma With his coca leaves and pearls In his halls he often wondered With the secrets of the worlds And his subjects Gathered around him Like the leaves around a tree In their clothes of many colors For the angry gods to see And the women all were beautiful And the men stood Straight and strong They offered life in sacrifice So that others could go on Hate was just a legend And war was never known The people worked together And they lifted many stones They carried them To the flat lands And they died along the way But they built up With their bare hands What we still can&#39;t do today And I know she&#39;s living there And she loves me to this day I still can&#39;t remember when Or how I lost my way He came dancing across the water Cortez, Cortez What a killer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down by the river</title>
      <link>/songs/down-by-the-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/down-by-the-river/</guid>
      <description>Be on my side, I&#39;ll be on your side, baby There is no reason for you to hide It&#39;s so hard for me staying here all alone When you could be taking me for a ride. Yeah, she could drag me over the rainbow, send me away Down by the river I shot my baby Down by the river, Dead, oh, shot her dead. You take my hand, I&#39;ll take your hand Together we may get away This much madness is too much sorrow It&#39;s impossible to make it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The needle and the damage done</title>
      <link>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</guid>
      <description>Intro: D D/C D/B D/Bb C C7 Esus4 E D D/C I caught you knockin&#39; at my cellar door D/B D/Bb &amp;quot;I love you, baby. Can I have some more?&amp;quot; C F Esus4 E Ooh, ooh, the damage done I hit the city and I lost my band I watched the needle take another man Gone, gone, the damage done [Repeat Intro] I sing the song, because I love the man I know that some of you don&#39;t understand Milk-blood to keep from running out I&#39;ve seen the needle and the damage done A little part of it in everyone But every junkie&#39;s like a settin&#39; sun  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>