<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name&amp;rsquo;s Hansen. I&amp;rsquo;m an ocean scientist and musician. See my personal website for more details about my work. This website is built in Hugo and based heavily off of the Xmin template. It is currently hosted on GitHub, and the source code is available here. Please feel free to share and use as you see fit, and don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to get in touch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ain&#39;t no sunshine</title>
      <link>/songs/aint-no-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/aint-no-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone It&#39;s not warm when she&#39;s away Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And she&#39;s always gone too long Anytime she goes away Wonder this time where she&#39;s gone Wonder if she&#39;s gone to stay Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And this house just ain&#39;t no home Anytime she goes away And I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, Hey, I oughtta leave young thing alone But ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone Only darkness every day Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And this house just ain&#39;t no home Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angel from Montgomery</title>
      <link>/songs/angel-from-montgomery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/angel-from-montgomery/</guid>
      <description>G C G C G C D C G C G C I am an old woman named after my mother G C D G My old man is another child that&#39;s grown old If dreams were lightning thunder was desire This old house would have burnt down a long time ago G F C G Make me an angel that flies from Montgom&#39;ry G F C G Make me a poster of an old rodeo Just give me one thing that I can hold on to To believe in this living is just a hard way to go When I was a young girl well, I had me a cowboy He weren&#39;t much to look at, just free rambling man But that was a long time and no matter how I try The years just flow by like a broken down dam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badfish</title>
      <link>/songs/badfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/badfish/</guid>
      <description>When you grab a hold of me Tell me that I&#39;ll never be set free But I&#39;m a parasite, Creep and crawl I step into the night. Two pints of booze Tell me are you a badfish too? Are you a badfish too? Ain&#39;t got no money to spend I hope the night will never end Lord knows I&#39;m weak Won&#39;t somebody get me off of this reef Baby you&#39;re a big blue whale Grab the reef when all duck diving fails I swim, but wish I&#39;d never learned The water&#39;s too polluted with the germs I dive deep when it&#39;s ten feet overhead Grab the reef underneath my bed (it&#39;s underneath my bed) Ain&#39;t got no quarrels with God Ain&#39;t got no time to grow old Lord knows I&#39;m weak Won&#39;t somebody get me off of this reef [Solo] Ain&#39;t got no quarrels with God Ain&#39;t got no time to get old Lord knows I&#39;m weak Won&#39;t somebody get me off of this reef  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackbird</title>
      <link>/songs/blackbird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/blackbird/</guid>
      <description>Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these broken wings and learn to fly All your life You were only waiting for this moment to arise Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these sunken eyes and learn to see All your life You were only waiting for this moment to be free Blackbird fly, blackbird fly Into the light of the dark black night Blackbird fly, blackbird fly Into the light of the dark black night Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these broken wings and learn to fly All your life You were only waiting for this moment to arise You were only waiting for this moment to arise You were only waiting for this moment to arise  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come together</title>
      <link>/songs/come-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/come-together/</guid>
      <description>Here come old flat top He come groovin&#39; up slowly He got joo joo eyeballs He one holy roller He got hair down to his knee Got to be a joker He just do what he please He wear no shoeshine He got toe jam football He got monkey finger He shoot Coca-Cola He say I know you, you know me One thing I can tell you is You got to be free Come together, right now Over me He bad production He got walrus gumboot He got Ono sideboard He one spinal cracker He got feet down below his knee Hold you in his armchair You can feel his disease Come together, right now Over me He roller coaster He got early warning He got muddy water He one Mojo filter He say one and one and one is three Got to be good looking &#39;Cause he&#39;s so hard to see Come together right now Over me Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah Come together, yeah  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cortez the killer</title>
      <link>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/cortez-the-killer/</guid>
      <description>He came dancing across the water With his galleons and guns Looking for the new world In that palace in the sun On the shore lay Montezuma With his coca leaves and pearls In his halls he often wondered With the secrets of the worlds And his subjects Gathered around him Like the leaves around a tree In their clothes of many colors For the angry gods to see And the women all were beautiful And the men stood Straight and strong They offered life in sacrifice So that others could go on Hate was just a legend And war was never known The people worked together And they lifted many stones They carried them To the flat lands And they died along the way But they built up With their bare hands What we still can&#39;t do today And I know she&#39;s living there And she loves me to this day I still can&#39;t remember when Or how I lost my way He came dancing across the water Cortez, Cortez What a killer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dock of the bay</title>
      <link>/songs/dock-of-the-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/dock-of-the-bay/</guid>
      <description>Sittin&#39; in the mornin&#39; sun I&#39;ll be sittin&#39; when the evenin&#39; comes Watchin&#39; the ships roll in Then I watch &#39;em roll away again I&#39;m sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay Watchin&#39; the tide, roll away I&#39;m sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay Wastin&#39; time I left my home in Georgia And I headed for the Frisco Bay &#39;Cause I&#39;ve got nothin&#39; to live for Looks like nothin&#39;s gonna come my way, so I&#39;m just come sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay Watchin&#39; the tide roll away I&#39;m sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay, Wastin&#39; time Looks like nothin&#39;s gonna change Everything seems to stay the same I can&#39;t do what ten people tell me to do So I guess I&#39;ll remain the same I&#39;m sittin&#39; here restin&#39; my bones And this loneliness won&#39;t leave me alone This two thousand miles I roamed Just to make this dock my home Now I&#39;m just sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay Watchin&#39; the tide roll away Sittin&#39; on the dock of the bay Wastin&#39; time  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down by the river</title>
      <link>/songs/down-by-the-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/down-by-the-river/</guid>
      <description>Be on my side, I&#39;ll be on your side, baby There is no reason for you to hide It&#39;s so hard for me staying here all alone When you could be taking me for a ride. Yeah, she could drag me over the rainbow, send me away Down by the river I shot my baby Down by the river, Dead, oh, shot her dead. You take my hand, I&#39;ll take your hand Together we may get away This much madness is too much sorrow It&#39;s impossible to make it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman behind the counter in a small town</title>
      <link>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</guid>
      <description>I seem to recognize your face Haunting, familiar yet I can&#39;t seem to place it Cannot find the candle of thought to light your name Lifetimes are catching up with me All these changes taking place I wish I&#39;d seen the place But no one&#39;s ever taken me Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away I swear, I recognize your breath Memories like fingerprints are slowly raising Me, you wouldn&#39;t recall for I&#39;m not my former It&#39;s hard when you&#39;re stuck upon the shelf I changed by not changing at all Small town predicts my fate Perhaps that&#39;s what no one wants to see I just want to scream hello My God it&#39;s been so long Never dreamed you&#39;d return But now here you are and here I am Hearts and thoughts they fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feelin&#39; alright</title>
      <link>/songs/feelin-alright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/feelin-alright/</guid>
      <description>Seems I got to have a change of scene &#39;Cause every night I have the strangest dreams Imprisoned by the way it could have been Left here on my own or so it seems I got to leave before I start to scream But someone&#39;s locked the door and took the key You feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Well, you feelin&#39; alright? I&#39;m not feelin&#39; too good myself Boy you sure took me for one big ride Even now I sit and wonder why And when I think of you I start myself to cry out I just can&#39;t waste my time, I must keep dry Gotta stop believin&#39; in all your lies &#39;Cause there&#39;s too much to do before I die, hey You feelin&#39; alright?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire and rain</title>
      <link>/songs/fire-and-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/fire-and-rain/</guid>
      <description>Just yesterday morning they let me know you were gone Susanne the plans they made put an end to you I walked out this morning and I wrote down this song I just can&#39;t remember who to send it to I&#39;ve seen fire and I&#39;ve seen rain I&#39;ve seen sunny days that I thought would never end I&#39;ve seen lonely times when I could not find a friend But I always thought that I&#39;d see you again Won&#39;t you look down upon me, jesus You&#39;ve got to help me make a stand You&#39;ve just got to see me through another day My body&#39;s aching and my time is at hand And I won&#39;t make it any other way Oh, I&#39;ve seen fire and I&#39;ve seen rain I&#39;ve seen sunny days that I thought would never end I&#39;ve seen lonely times when I could not find a friend But I always thought that I&#39;d see you again Been walking my mind to an easy time my back turned towards the sun Lord knows when the cold wind blows it&#39;ll turn your head around Well, there&#39;s hours of time on the telephone line to talk about things To come Sweet dreams and flying machines in pieces on the ground Oh, I&#39;ve seen fire and I&#39;ve seen rain I&#39;ve seen sunny days that I thought would never end I&#39;ve seen lonely times when I could not find a friend But I always thought that I&#39;d see you, baby, one more time again, now Thought I&#39;d see you one more time again There&#39;s just a few things coming my way this time around, now Thought I&#39;d see you, thought I&#39;d see you fire and rain, now  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folsom prison blues</title>
      <link>/songs/folsom-prison-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/folsom-prison-blues/</guid>
      <description>I hear the train a comin&#39; It&#39;s rollin&#39; &#39;round the bend, And I ain&#39;t seen the sunshine Since, I don&#39;t know when I&#39;m stuck in Folsom Prison And time keeps draggin&#39; on But that train keeps a-rollin&#39; On down to San Antone When I was just a baby My Mama told me, &amp;quot;Son Always be a good boy Don&#39;t ever play with guns, &amp;quot; But I shot a man in Reno Just to watch him die When I hear that whistle blowin&#39; I hang my head and cry I bet there&#39;s rich folks eatin&#39; In a fancy dining car They&#39;re probably drinkin&#39; coffee And smokin&#39; big cigars But I know I had it comin&#39; I know I can&#39;t be free But those people keep a-movin&#39; And that&#39;s what tortures me Well, if they freed me from this prison If that railroad train was mine I bet I&#39;d move out over a little Farther down the line Far from Folsom Prison That&#39;s where I want to stay And I&#39;d let that lonesome whistle Blow my blues away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frosty the snowman</title>
      <link>/songs/frosty-the-snowman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/frosty-the-snowman/</guid>
      <description>G Thumpety thump thump, thumpety thump thump, D7 Look at Frosty go. Thumpety thump thump, thumpety thump thump, G over the hills of snow...Oh...Oh...over the hills of snow. G C G Frosty the Snow Man, was a jolly happy soul C G With a corn-cob pipe and a button nose D G and two eyes made out of coal. G C G Frosty the Snow Man, is a fairy tale they say C G He was made of snow but the children know C D7 G how he came to life one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Joe</title>
      <link>/songs/hey-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/hey-joe/</guid>
      <description>Hey Joe, where you goin&#39; with that gun of yours? Hey Joe, I said where you goin&#39; with that gun in your hand, oh I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man I&#39;m goin&#39; down to shoot my old lady You know I caught her messin&#39; &#39;round with another man And that ain&#39;t too cool Huh, hey Joe, I heard you shot your mamma down You shot her down now Hey Joe, I heard you shot your lady down You shot her down in the ground, yeah Yeah Yes, I did, I shot her You know I caught her messin&#39; round, messin&#39; round town Yes I did, I shot her You know I caught my old lady messin&#39; &#39;round town And I gave her the gun And I shot her Alright Shoot her one more time again, baby Yeah Oh, dig it Oh, alright Hey Joe Where you gonna run to now, where you gonna go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I can&#39;t make you love me</title>
      <link>/songs/i-cant-make-you-love-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/i-cant-make-you-love-me/</guid>
      <description>   C Em Em C C G/B Am C Em Turn down the lights Em C Turn down the bed C G/B Em Am Turn down these voices inside my head C Em Lay down with me Em C Tell me no lies C G/B Em Am Just hold me close, don&#39;t patronize D Don&#39;t patronize me C G C &#39;Cause I can&#39;t make you love me if you don&#39;t C G G/B C You can&#39;t make your heart feel something it won&#39;t Em C D/F# Em Here in the dark, in these final hours Em C D/F# Em I will lay down my heart and I&#39;ll feel the power Am D But you won&#39;t, no you won&#39;t C G C &#39;Cause I can&#39;t make you love me, if you don&#39;t C Em Em C C G/B Am I&#39;ll close my eyes, then I won&#39;t see The love you don&#39;t feel when you&#39;re holding me Morning will come and I&#39;ll do what&#39;s right Just give me till then to give up this fight And I will give up this fight &#39;Cause I can&#39;t make you love me if you don&#39;t You can&#39;t make your heart feel something it won&#39;t Here in the dark, in these final hours I will lay down my heart and I&#39;ll feel the power But you won&#39;t, no you won&#39;t &#39;Cause I can&#39;t make you love me, if you don&#39;t  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wanna be your lover</title>
      <link>/songs/i-wanna-be-your-lover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/i-wanna-be-your-lover/</guid>
      <description>I ain&#39;t got no money I ain&#39;t like those other guys you hang around It&#39;s kinda funny But they always seem to let you down And I get discouraged &#39;Cause I never see you anymore And I need your love, babe That&#39;s all I&#39;m living for, yeah I didn&#39;t want to pressure you, baby But all I ever wanted to do I want to be your lover I want to be the only one that makes you come, running I want to be your lover I want to turn you on, turn you out All night long, make you shout Oh, lover, yeah!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle bells</title>
      <link>/songs/jingle-bells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/jingle-bells/</guid>
      <description>G Dashing through the snow C In a one horse open sleigh D O&#39;er the fields we go G Laughing all the way G Bells on bob tails ring C Making spirits bright C D What fun it is to laugh and sing C G A sleighing song tonight G Oh, jingle bells, jingle bells G Jingle all the way C G Oh, what fun it is to ride D D In a one horse open sleigh G Jingle bells, jingle bells G Jingle all the way C G Oh, what fun it is to ride D C G In a one horse open sleigh (lesser-known verses follow with the same chord structure) A day or two ago I thought I&#39;d take a ride And soon, Miss Fanny Bright Was seated by my side, The horse was lean and lank Misfortune seemed his lot He got into a drifted bank And then we got upsot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King of the road</title>
      <link>/songs/king-of-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/king-of-the-road/</guid>
      <description>Trailer for sale or rent, rooms to let, fifty cents. No phone, no pool, no pets, I ain&#39;t got no cigarettes Ah, but, two hours of pushin&#39; broom Buys an eight by twelve four-bit room I&#39;m a man of means by no means, king of the road. Third boxcar, midnight train, destination, Bangor, Maine. Old worn out clothes and shoes, I don&#39;t pay no union dues, I smoke old stogies I have found short, but not too big around I&#39;m a man of means by no means, king of the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layla</title>
      <link>/songs/layla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/layla/</guid>
      <description>What&#39;ll you do when you get lonely And nobody&#39;s waiting by your side? You&#39;ve been running and hiding much too long. You know it&#39;s just your foolish pride. Layla, you&#39;ve got me on my knees. Layla, I&#39;m begging, darling please. Layla, darling won&#39;t you ease my worried mind. I tried to give you consolation When your old man had let you down. Like a fool, I fell in love with you, Turned my whole world upside down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow</title>
      <link>/songs/let-it-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/let-it-snow/</guid>
      <description>G Oh, the weather outside is frightful, D But the fire is so delightful, Am E7 Am And since we&#39;ve no place to go, D7 Bm G Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow. G It doesn&#39;t show signs of stopping, D And I brought some corn for popping. Am E7 Am The lights are turned way down low, D7 Bm G Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow D When we finally kiss good night, Em A7 D How I&#39;ll hate going out in the storm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little wing</title>
      <link>/songs/little-wing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/little-wing/</guid>
      <description>Well she&#39;s walking through the clouds With a circus mind That&#39;s running wild Butterflies and zebras and moonbeams And fairly tales, That&#39;s all she ever thinks about Riding the wind When I&#39;m sad she comes to me With a thousand smiles She gives to me free It&#39;s alright, she says It&#39;s alright Take anything you want from me Anything Fly on, little wing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely day</title>
      <link>/songs/lovely-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/lovely-day/</guid>
      <description>When I wake up in the morning, love And the sunlight hurts my eyes And something without warning, love Bears heavy on my mind Then I look at you And the world&#39;s alright with me Just one look at you And I know it&#39;s gonna be A lovely day A lovely day When the day that lies ahead of me Seems impossible to face When someone else instead of me Always seems to know the way Then I look at you And the world&#39;s alright with me Just one look at you And I know it&#39;s gonna be A lovely day A lovely day When the day that lies ahead of me Seems impossible to face When someone else instead of me Always seems to know the way Then I look at you And the world&#39;s alright with me Just one look at you And I know it&#39;s gonna be A lovely day A lovely day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luckiest man</title>
      <link>/songs/luckiest-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/luckiest-man/</guid>
      <description>My whole saturday and sunday too I was thinking about ways not to lose I lay down my weapons is what I&#39;ve done Too late to hide, feet too soft to run But people say I&#39;m the luckiest man Yeah they say Running is useless and fighting is foolish You&#39;re not gonna win but still you&#39;re the luckiest man you&#39;re up against And too many horses and mysterious forces What you don&#39;t know is you are the luckiest man You&#39;re the luckiest man I done talked to the devil when he calls my name But sometimes when I&#39;m losing it all seems the same And when I fall I&#39;m back up again Just to slip on the same mistakes and slide right back in But people say I&#39;m the luckiest man Yeah they say Running is useless and fighting is foolish You&#39;re not gonna win but still you&#39;re the luckiest man you&#39;re up against And too many horses and mysterious forces What you don&#39;t know is you are the luckiest man You&#39;re the luckiest man Try to keep my faith and keep my mind Hate to lose either one when the whip cracks behind And I can&#39;t help but mourning just a little each night People say everything is gonna be alright They say I&#39;m the luckiest man Yeah they say That running is useless and fighting is foolish You&#39;re not gonna win but still you&#39;re the luckiest man you&#39;re up against And too many horses and mysterious forces What you don&#39;t know is you are the luckiest man You&#39;re the luckiest man You&#39;re the luckiest man  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many rivers to cross</title>
      <link>/songs/many-rivers-to-cross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/many-rivers-to-cross/</guid>
      <description>Many rivers to cross But I can&#39;t seem to find my way over Wandering I am lost As I travel along the white cliffs of Dover Many rivers to cross And it&#39;s only my will that keeps me alive I&#39;ve been licked, washed up for years And I merely survive because of my pride And this loneliness won&#39;t leave me alone It&#39;s such a drag to be on your own My woman left me and she didn&#39;t say why Well I guess, I have to try Many rivers to cross But just where to begin, I&#39;m playing for time There are times I find myself Thinking of committing some dreadful crime Yes, I&#39;ve got many rivers to cross But I can&#39;t seem to find my way over Wandering I am lost As I travel along the white cliffs of Dover  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melissa</title>
      <link>/songs/melissa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/melissa/</guid>
      <description>Crossroads, seem to come and go, yeah The gypsy flies from coast to coast Knowing many, loving none Bearing sorrow, having fun But, back home he&#39;ll always run To sweet Melissa Freight train, each car looks the same, all the same And no one knows the gypsy&#39;s name And no one hears his lonely sighs There are no blankets where he lies Lord, in his deepest dreams the gypsy flies With sweet Melissa Again, the mornin&#39;s come Again, he&#39;s on the run A sunbeam&#39;s shinin&#39; through his hair Fear not to have a care Well, pick up your gear and gypsy roll on Roll on Crossroads, will you ever let him go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nearness of you</title>
      <link>/songs/nearness-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/nearness-of-you/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s not the pale moon that excites me That thrills and delights me Oh no, it&#39;s just the nearness of you It isn&#39;t your sweet conversation That brings this sensation Oh no, it&#39;s just the nearness of you When you&#39;re in my arms And I feel you so close to me All my wildest dreams came true I need no soft lights to enchant me If you will only grant me The right to hold you ever so tight And to feel in the night The nearness of you  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No expectations</title>
      <link>/songs/no-expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/no-expectations/</guid>
      <description>Take me to the station And put me on a train I&#39;ve got no expectations To pass through here again Once I was a rich man and Now I am so poor But never in my sweet short life Have I felt like this before You heart is like a diamond You throw your pearls at swine And as I watch you leaving me You pack my peace of mind Our love was like the water That splashes on a stone Our love is like our music It&#39;s here, and then it&#39;s gone So take me to the airport And put me on a plane I&#39;ve got no expectations To pass through here again  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple rain</title>
      <link>/songs/purple-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/purple-rain/</guid>
      <description>   I never meant to cause you any sorrow I never meant to cause you any pain I only wanted to one time to see you laughing I only wanted to see you Laughing in the purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain I only wanted to see you Bathing in the purple rain I never wanted to be your weekend lover I only wanted to be some kind of friend Baby, I could never steal you from another It&#39;s such a shame our friendship had to end Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain I only wanted to see you Underneath the purple rain Honey, I know, I know I know times are changing It&#39;s time we all reach out For something new, that means you too You say you want a leader But you can&#39;t seem to make up your mind I think you better close it And let me guide you to the purple rain Purple rain, purple rain Purple rain, purple rain If you know what I&#39;m singing about up here C&#39;mon, raise your hand Purple rain, purple rain I only want to see you Only want to see you In the purple rain  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redemption song</title>
      <link>/songs/redemption-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/redemption-song/</guid>
      <description>Old pirates, yes, they rob I Sold I to the merchant ships Minutes after they took I From the bottomless pit But my hand was made strong By the hand of the Almighty We forward in this generation Triumphantly Won&#39;t you help to sing These songs of freedom? &#39;Cause all I ever have Redemption songs Redemption songs Emancipate yourselves from mental slavery None but ourselves can free our minds Have no fear for atomic energy &#39;Cause none of them can stop the time How long shall they kill our prophets While we stand aside and look?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>River of deceit</title>
      <link>/songs/river-of-deceit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/river-of-deceit/</guid>
      <description>My pain is self-chosen At least, so the prophet says I could either burn Or cut off my pride and buy some time A head full of lies is the weight, tied to my waist The river of deceit pulls down, oh oh The only direction we flow is down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down My pain is self-chosen At least I believe it to be I could either drown Or pull off my skin and swim to shore Now I can grow a beautiful shell for all to see The river of deceit pulls down, yeah The only direction we flow is down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down The pain is self-chosen, yeah Our pain is self-chosen Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down Down, oh down  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockin&#39; around the Christmas tree</title>
      <link>/songs/rockin-around-the-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/rockin-around-the-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>C G Rocking around the Christmas tree at the Christmas party hop G C Mistletoe hung where you can see every couple tries to stop C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, let the Christmas spirit ring G C Later we&#39;ll have some pumpkin pie and we&#39;ll do some caroling F Em You will get a sentimental feeling when you hear Am D G Voices singing let&#39;s be jolly, deck the halls with boughs of holly C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, have a happy holiday G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old-fashioned way F Em You will get a sentimental feeling when you hear Am D G Voices singing let&#39;s be jolly, deck the halls with boughs of holly C G Rocking around the Christmas tree, have a happy holiday G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old-fashioned way G C G C Everyone dancing merrily in the new old - fa - shioned way  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer</title>
      <link>/songs/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer/</guid>
      <description>F Em Dm C You know Dasher and Dancer and Prancer and Vixen F Em Dm C Comet and Cupid and Donner and Blitzen Am Dm But do you recall D7 G7 The most famous reindeer of all? C Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer G Had a very shiny nose G And if you ever saw it C You would even say it glows C All of the other reindeer G Used to laugh and call him names G They never let poor Rudolph C Join in any reindeer games F Em Then one foggy Christmas Eve Dm7 G C Santa came to say: G &amp;quot;Rudolph with your nose so bright D7 G7 Won&#39;t you guide my sleigh tonight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus is coming to town</title>
      <link>/songs/santa-claus-is-coming-to-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/santa-claus-is-coming-to-town/</guid>
      <description>Intro: |C Am |Dm |C |G | Verse 1: C F You better watch out, you&#39;d better not cry, C F you&#39;d better not pout, I&#39;m telling you why, C Am Dm G C Santa Claus is coming to town. (Gather &#39;round...) C F He&#39;s making a list and checking it twice, C F C Am Dm G C gonna find out who&#39;s naughty and nice, Santa Claus is coming to town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something</title>
      <link>/songs/something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/something/</guid>
      <description>Something in the way she moves Attracts me like no other lover Something in the way she woos me I don&#39;t want to leave her now You know I believe and how Somewhere in her smile she knows That I don&#39;t need no other lover Something in her style that shows me I don&#39;t want to leave her now You know I believe and how You&#39;re asking me will my love grow I don&#39;t know, I don&#39;t know You stick around and it may show I don&#39;t know, I don&#39;t know [Solo] Something in the way she knows And all I have to do is think of her Something in the things she shows me I don&#39;t want to leave her now You know I believe and how  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Susie Q</title>
      <link>/songs/susie-q/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/susie-q/</guid>
      <description>Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q baby I love you, Susie Q I like the way you walk I like the way you talk I like the way you walk I like the way you talk, Susie Q Well, say that you&#39;ll be true Well, say that you&#39;ll be true Well, say that you&#39;ll be true and never leave me blue, Susie Q Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine, Well, say that you&#39;ll be mine, baby all the time, Susie Q Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q, baby I love you, Susie Q I like the way you walk I like the way you talk I like the way you walk I like the way you talk, Susie Q Oh Susie Q, oh Susie Q Oh Susie Q, baby I love you, Susie Q  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The muse</title>
      <link>/songs/the-muse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/the-muse/</guid>
      <description>As I sit on the edge of this never made bed Old guitar in my lap a new tune in my head There she stands in the doorway just brushin&#39; her hair It&#39;s my beautiful muse in her underwear And if I was thinkin&#39; I’d be thinkin&#39; thank God whoever you are For the muse and this old guitar Times like these so sweet and so true Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do As I sit on the end of this dirty old bar Tryin’ to work some things out and not gettin&#39; too far And I drown out the voices that are keepin&#39; me down There’s a muse all alone on the other side of town And if I was thinkin&#39; I’d be thinkin&#39; thank God whoever you are For all the whiskey in this dirty old bar Times like these so sad but so true Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do As I sit on the bed in this hospital room Sheddin’ a tear for the bride and groom The tiniest voice starts to bellow and cry It’s my finest work yet if today I should die And if I was thinkin&#39; I’d be thinkin&#39; thank God whoever you are For the muse and the miracle right here in my arms Times like these so sweet and so true Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do Thinkin’s the last thing that you wanna do  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The needle and the damage done</title>
      <link>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/the-needle-and-the-damage-done/</guid>
      <description>Intro: D D/C D/B D/Bb C C7 Esus4 E D D/C I caught you knockin&#39; at my cellar door D/B D/Bb &amp;quot;I love you, baby. Can I have some more?&amp;quot; C F Esus4 E Ooh, ooh, the damage done I hit the city and I lost my band I watched the needle take another man Gone, gone, the damage done [Repeat Intro] I sing the song, because I love the man I know that some of you don&#39;t understand Milk-blood to keep from running out I&#39;ve seen the needle and the damage done A little part of it in everyone But every junkie&#39;s like a settin&#39; sun  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The way you make me feel</title>
      <link>/songs/the-way-you-make-me-feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/the-way-you-make-me-feel/</guid>
      <description>Hey pretty baby with the high heels on You give me fever Like I&#39;ve never, ever known You&#39;re just a product of loveliness I like the groove of your walk, Your talk, your dress I feel your fever From miles around I&#39;ll pick you up in my car And we&#39;ll paint the town Just kiss me baby And tell me twice That you&#39;re the one for me The way you make me feel You really turn me on You knock me off of my feet My lonely days are gone I like the feelin&#39; you&#39;re givin&#39; me Just hold me baby and I&#39;m in ecstasy Oh I&#39;ll be workin&#39; from nine to five To buy you things to keep you by my side I never felt so in love before Just promise baby, you&#39;ll love me forevermore I swear I&#39;m keepin&#39; you satisfied &#39;Cause you&#39;re the one for me The way you make me feel You really turn me on You knock me off of my feet My lonely days are gone, Go on girl!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuner</title>
      <link>/tuner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tuner/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under the bridge</title>
      <link>/songs/under-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/under-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I feel Like I don&#39;t have a partner Sometimes I feel Like my only friend Is the city I live in The city of angels Lonely as I am Together we cry I drive on her streets &#39;Cause she&#39;s my companion I walk through her hills &#39;Cause she knows who I am She sees my good deeds And she kisses me windy I never worry Now that is a lie I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way (yeah yeah) It&#39;s hard to believe That there&#39;s nobody out there It&#39;s hard to believe That I&#39;m all alone At least I have her love The city she loves me Lonely as I am Together we cry I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way I don&#39;t ever want to feel Like I did that day Take me to the place I love Take me all the way (yeah yeah) Ooh no (no no yeah yeah) Love me I say yeah yeah Under the bridge downtown Is were I drew some blood Under the bridge downtown I could not get enough Under the bridge downtown Forgot about my love Under the bridge downtown I gave my life away (yeah yeah) Ooh no (no no yeah yeah) Here I stay yeah yeah Here I stay  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use me</title>
      <link>/songs/use-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/use-me/</guid>
      <description>My friends feel it&#39;s their appointed duty They keep trying to tell me all you want to do is use me But my answer yeah to all that use me stuff Is I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up My brother sit me right down and he talked to me He told me that I ought not to let you just walk on me And I&#39;m sure he meant well yeah but when our talk was through I said brother if you only knew you&#39;d wish that you were in my shoes You just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Oh sometimes yeah it&#39;s true you really do abuse me You get in a crowd of high class people and then you act real rude to me But oh baby baby baby baby when you love me I can&#39;t get enough I and I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Talking about you using me but it all depends on what you do It ain&#39;t too bad the way you&#39;re using me &#39;Cause I sure am using you to do the things you do Ah ha to do the things you do  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whipping post</title>
      <link>/songs/whipping-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/whipping-post/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been run down and I&#39;ve been lied to. And I don&#39;t know why, I let that mean woman make me a fool. She took all my money, wrecks my new car. Now she&#39;s with one of my good time buddies, They&#39;re drinkin in some cross-town bar. Sometimes I feel, sometimes I feel, Like I been tied to the whippin&#39; post. Tied to the whippin&#39; post, tied to the whippin&#39; post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild horses</title>
      <link>/songs/wild-horses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/wild-horses/</guid>
      <description>Childhood living is easy to do The things you wanted I bought them for you Graceless lady you know who I am You know I can&#39;t let you slide through my hands Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away I watched you suffer a dull aching pain Now you&#39;ve decided to show me the same No sweeping exit or offstage lines Could make me feel bitter or treat you unkind Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away I know I&#39;ve dreamed you a sin and a lie I have my freedom but I don&#39;t have much time Faith has been broken tears must be cried Let&#39;s do some living after we die Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses we&#39;ll ride them some day Wild horses couldn&#39;t drag me away Wild, wild horses we&#39;ll ride them some day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter wonderland</title>
      <link>/songs/winter-wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/winter-wonderland/</guid>
      <description> D Sleigh bells ring are you listening A In the lane snow is glistening A7 Em A A7 A beautiful sight we&#39;re happy tonight Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland D Gone away is the blue bird A In his place is the new bird A7 Em A A7 Hes singing our song as we go along Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland Chorus: F# B F# In the meadow we can build a snowman F# B F# Then pretend that he is Parson Brown A D A He&#39;ll say Are you married We&#39;ll say No man A7 E A But you can do the job when you&#39;re in town D Later on we&#39;ll conspire A As we dream by the fire A7 Em A A7 To face unafraid the plans that we made Bm A D Walking in a Winter Wonderland  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wish you were here</title>
      <link>/songs/wish-you-were-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/wish-you-were-here/</guid>
      <description>So, so you think you can tell Heaven from hell Blue skies from pain Can you tell a green field From a cold steel rail? A smile from a veil? Do you think you can tell? Did they get you to trade Your heroes for ghosts? Hot ashes for trees? Hot air for a cool breeze? Cold comfort for change? Did you exchange A walk on part in the war For a lead role in a cage?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>