<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Belt on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</title>
    <link>/tags/belt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Belt on Hansen&#39;s Songbook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/belt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ain&#39;t no sunshine</title>
      <link>/songs/aint-no-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/aint-no-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone It&#39;s not warm when she&#39;s away Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And she&#39;s always gone too long Anytime she goes away Wonder this time where she&#39;s gone Wonder if she&#39;s gone to stay Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And this house just ain&#39;t no home Anytime she goes away And I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, I know, I know, I know I know, I know, Hey, I oughtta leave young thing alone But ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone Only darkness every day Ain&#39;t no sunshine when she&#39;s gone And this house just ain&#39;t no home Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away Anytime she goes away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman behind the counter in a small town</title>
      <link>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/elderly-woman-behind-the-counter-in-a-small-town/</guid>
      <description>I seem to recognize your face Haunting, familiar yet I can&#39;t seem to place it Cannot find the candle of thought to light your name Lifetimes are catching up with me All these changes taking place I wish I&#39;d seen the place But no one&#39;s ever taken me Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away I swear, I recognize your breath Memories like fingerprints are slowly raising Me, you wouldn&#39;t recall for I&#39;m not my former It&#39;s hard when you&#39;re stuck upon the shelf I changed by not changing at all Small town predicts my fate Perhaps that&#39;s what no one wants to see I just want to scream hello My God it&#39;s been so long Never dreamed you&#39;d return But now here you are and here I am Hearts and thoughts they fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade, fade away Hearts and thoughts they fade away  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use me</title>
      <link>/songs/use-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/use-me/</guid>
      <description>My friends feel it&#39;s their appointed duty They keep trying to tell me all you want to do is use me But my answer yeah to all that use me stuff Is I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up My brother sit me right down and he talked to me He told me that I ought not to let you just walk on me And I&#39;m sure he meant well yeah but when our talk was through I said brother if you only knew you&#39;d wish that you were in my shoes You just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Oh sometimes yeah it&#39;s true you really do abuse me You get in a crowd of high class people and then you act real rude to me But oh baby baby baby baby when you love me I can&#39;t get enough I and I want to spread the news that if it feels this good getting used Oh you just keep on using me until you use me up Until you use me up Talking about you using me but it all depends on what you do It ain&#39;t too bad the way you&#39;re using me &#39;Cause I sure am using you to do the things you do Ah ha to do the things you do  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whipping post</title>
      <link>/songs/whipping-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/songs/whipping-post/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been run down and I&#39;ve been lied to. And I don&#39;t know why, I let that mean woman make me a fool. She took all my money, wrecks my new car. Now she&#39;s with one of my good time buddies, They&#39;re drinkin in some cross-town bar. Sometimes I feel, sometimes I feel, Like I been tied to the whippin&#39; post. Tied to the whippin&#39; post, tied to the whippin&#39; post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>